Oh, Brian, we're so thrilled
your gay cousin, Jasper,
finally decided to come visit.
Me, too. It's been way too long.
Anyway, thanks for putting him up.
No problem, Brian.
It's great to have visitors.
Except for that time
Moby-Dick stayed with us.
Do you have any Raisin Bran?
Uh, oh, no, sorry.
Well, can you go get me some?
Uh, boy, that's kind of a pain in the...
We do have...
We got Total, and we got some raisins.
I mean, you could,
like, mix those together.
I mean, it would be kind
of like Raisin Bran.
Mmm, yeah, but it's not.
It would be like Raisin Bran,
but it's not Raisin Bran.
That would be like Total with raisins in it.
That's just splitting hairs here.
It's not really doing it for me.
What time did you say your flight was?
Oh, no locks.
Thank you, Homeland Security.
Hey, bud, take a break.
I'll take over. Go smoke a fatty.
Thanks.
This is
Sierra Tango 817,
Matthew McConaughey's private jet,
requesting permission to land.
Matthew McConaughey?
Oh, sorry, Sierra Tango 817.
All our runways are filled.
But it looks empty from up here.
We're almost out of fuel.
No, no. No room at all.
But, lucky for you,
there's a big, new airport
out in the middle of the ocean.
Keep going. You can't miss it.
Roger that.
Oops. Well, look at it this way.
I just got you on next year's
Oscar telecast.
You'll be right after Ron Howard!
Just messing with you, Ron.
Or maybe not!
No, seriously, I am.
Or am I?
No.
Oh, there's Jasper's plane.
- Where?
- Third one in line.
Oh, it's one of them new niche airlines.
Hey, Cousin!
Hey, Jasper!
Everybody, this is Ricardo,
from the Philippines and my kitchen floor.
How was your flight?
Oh, torture!
Five hours on my moneymaker,
sitting across from a gaggle of sailors
flying home on leave.
Here I am in a committed relationship,
and all I can think about
is having a piece of Navy cake.
"Hello. Who's that on the phone?"
"Temptation!"
How does he
always get my number? I don't know.
Anyway, I got big news,
and I'll tell you over dinner. Greek. On me.
But enough about last weekend.
I'm terrible!
This idiot
will fit in with our family
as badly as Peter
fit in with The Proclaimers.
I'm singing! I'm singing!
Hey, Chris, this field trip
is your chance, man.
Alyssa is all alone.
She's so pretty that if your Hacky Sack
were my private parts,
I'd let her do that to them.
What? Kick them around?
Um, wait. Yes.
Welcome, citizens.
Today we commemorate
those brave Quahog soldiers
who perished in the recent Gulf conflict.
I can think
of no greater tribute to their memories
than this solid gold statue
of Dig 'Em, the Sugar Smacks frog.
What is that?
The spirit of America
is epitomized by his inspiring motto,
'"Smack, smack, Sugar Smack.
'"Give me a smack,
and I'll smack you back. '"
I'd also like to take this opportunity
to announce extreme budget cutbacks
having almost nothing to do
with this solid gold statue.
Have you ever seen
such a waste of the taxpayers' money?
You're talking to me!
This is more exciting than that time
me and my friends did mushrooms.
This is gonna be awesome!
You said it.
Man, you guys feel anything yet?
I feel kind of funny.
I got a bellyache.
We shouldn't have did this, man.
Lois, darling, those earrings are delicious.
Total kitsch.
Like an Andy Warhol wet dream.
I'm opening a museum
and putting you in it, they're that fabulous.
You think it's clever
talking like that, do you?
You think it's funny?
Talking about earrings, and using words
like "fabulous" and "delicious" and "wet. "
What's next? A workout
followed by a romp around a crowded room
while the music goes...
Oh, why did you stop?
Hey, Jasper, let me ask you something.
When you're in the shower at the "Y,"
is that just like
Supermarket Sweep for you guys,
or is there some kind of etiquette?
Peter, stop it.
God! You're more clueless than Popeye.
Sir, I think you should know
these growths on your forearms,
they're giant tumors.
Oh, dear.
Yeah, I'm surprised you haven't realized
this is not how a human being
is supposed to look.
And the speech thing,
and what you're doing with your eye...
Uh, you had a stroke
about seven years ago.
That you've managed
to be walking around all this time
is nothing short of a miracle.
I'd say about two months.
Okay, all right,
time for the big announcement.
Everyone, Ricardo and I
are getting married!
Oh, that is terrific!
It's about time you two settled down.
Oh, you hear that, Meg?
Guys can marry other guys now.
So... This is awkward, but, uh,
I mean, if they can do that,
that's pretty much it for you, isn't it?
I mean, you might as well pack it in.
Game over.
Alyssa, hi.
I was wondering if maybe you wanted
to do something sometime?
Sure, Chris.
I have a Young Republicans
meeting after school. You wanna come?
Oh, sure. What do you do at
a Young Republicans meeting?
We help those who already have
the means to help themselves.
Also, we perpetuate the ideal
that Jesus chose America
to destroy nonbelievers and brown people.
I don't understand what you're saying,
but somehow I feel safer.
Karl, this is Chris.
He wants to join our club.
Karl is our chancellor.
Well, Chris, we'd be happy to have you.
There's just one little rite of initiation.
Liberal chubby chaser!
Well, if you can't laugh at yourself...
I'm here at the parking lot
outside city hall,
where hundreds of citizens
have come out in protest
of the Mayor's decision to spend
the town's treasury on a gold frog.
I don't like it.
And I don't like
the contraction apostrophe-E-M.
As far as I'm concerned,
his name is Dig Them.
You're not welcome here, Dig Them.
I stand behind my decision.
This press conference is over.
I can't see you now.
I can't hear you now. You're not here now.
Well, there you have it. Back to you, Tom.
Thanks, Tom. Some damn fine reporting.
Damn fine. Diane?
Well, it's encouraging to know
that I'm not the only Mayor West
who's facing difficulties.
But what I need now is a diversion.
Let's see.
Mmm. "Jingle keys. "
My God! I'm a tomato!
And now back to
The Sound of Music.
Oh, thank heaven.
The von Trapp family escaped!
Reverend Mother, I have sinned.
What is this sin, my child?
Oh, well. No harm done.
I too have sinned, Mother.
Oh, my God!
That's Rolfe!
What the hell is wrong with you?
Hey, I didn't start this war, but it's on!
Oh, Lois, there you are.
Listen, Ricardo and I wanna thank you
for letting us have the wedding here.
Oh! You're having the wedding here?
Yeah. I hope that's okay, Lois.
I offered them the house.
Oh, uh, sure. No problem.
Hey, McButt the Crime Dog,
I heard you and your little chew toy
getting it on last night.
Keep it down.
Sorry, little man.
Ricardo and I were playing Clue,
and he got me in the bedroom
with a lead pipe.
Peter, I'm not sure I'm comfortable
having this wedding at the house.
Lois, I don't know what the big deal is.
So they're gay.
It's not like we're gonna have
a gay sex orgy in the living room.
That's not what I'm talking about.
I've got nothing against homosexuals.
I mean, I'll watch anything
with David Schwimmer.
But the idea of two men
actually getting married,
it just doesn't seem right.
Hey, I say who cares, you know?
If gays wanna get married
and be miserable like the rest of us,
I say we should let them.
Oh, no!
- What's wrong?
- Look.
Some breaking news today
when Mayor West announced he will sign
a citywide ban
on gay marriages next week.
While controversial, it has nonetheless
effectively distracted all of us
from the Dig 'Em fiasco.
- The what?
- I don't know. Something about a lizard.
And now this.
Look at that.
In the '30s, they called this
an Uncle Spinny Dervish.
- Really?
- I don't know. I'm just bored.
A ban on gay marriage? Oh, my God!
Matthew McConaughey?
Yeah, I'm looking for a guy named Stewie.
Chris, grab his legs. I gotta bury this thing.
- But I...
- Grab his legs!
I can't believe the wedding's off.
All I ever wanted was to get married
and make a home
with a skinny, hairless Filipino boy.
Isn't that the American dream?
Oh, don't give up yet, Jasper.
Mayor West only banned gay marriage
so he could distract
from the Dig 'Em scandal.
He won't get away with it.
Oh, Jasper, where'd you get
these brownies?
They're from a bakery
in the West Quahog gay district.
I thought they'd help my depression.
Oh, I can see why. Oh, my God,
they pack so much fudge into these.
And look at this. There's even
a couple of nuts lodged in there.
I'm going upstairs.
Oh, I've got to do something.
Jasper's always
been there for me when I've needed him.
I am gonna make Mayor West
change his mind.
But, Brian, the Bible says
gay marriage is an abomination.
Oh, don't give me
that Young Republican crap, Chris.
The Bible also says
a senior citizen built an ark
and rounded up two of every animal.
- Hey.
- Yeah?
What the hell is this?
Oh, you didn't really give
any specific guidelines about mating.
- Did you name it?
- What?
Did you name it?
Uh, yeah, he's Paul.
Yeah? Well, it's gonna be
a hell of a lot harder for you now,
because he's going the fuck overboard.
Hi, Glenn.
Uh, hey, will you sign
a petition to overturn
Mayor West's ban on gay marriage?
Gay marriage? Oh, come on,
two halves can't make a whole
without a hole.
Giggity Giggity Giggity Giggity.
You get off my property, you pervert.
Uh, Mr. Bottomtooth,
would you like to sign the petition?
Uh, I don't... What's the problem?
Ah! Okay. Thank you.
Chris, did you hear?
Some dog is going around town
trying to get support for gay marriage.
Oh, that's Brian. He's got a petition.
Really?
Chris, you've got to destroy that petition.
Why?
Because if you do,
I'll let you touch my boobs.
Is that good? Do I want that?
Oh, yeah, you want that.
Well, fantastic then.
How can I help you, Mrs. Griffin?
Well, I'm having a bit of a crisis.
I'm a very open-minded person,
and I've never
had any problem with gays before,
but something about
two gay people getting married,
I just don't think it's right.
Well, these questions are too big
to be decided by human beings.
Which is why God made this film.
You know, there's been
a lot of talk lately about homosexuals,
but how do you know what to believe?
Well, here are a few tips that
may help you tell when you've got a gay.
So, uh, what's your favorite
Madonna album?
I like her early work.
If his answer
is anything but '"I've never bought one, '"
you've got a gay.
Let's take a blood sample, Mr. Braga.
If instead of human blood,
you find a deadly corrosive acid,
you've got a gay.
Not this time, nancy-boy.
Well, that was interesting.
I also have My Giant with Billy Crystal.
Oh, God, no, no.
Well, we almost have enough signatures,
thanks to Quahog's gay district.
Lois, how'd you like to be
signature number 10,000?
- Brian, I can't sign this.
- Why not?
Well, because I don't believe
in gay marriage.
You don't believe...
Lois, that's ridiculous.
Gay people have every right
to get married.
Well, they certainly
have every right to be together,
but marriage should be
between a man and a woman.
Well, that's not how they
do it in West Quahog.
By the way, Lois,
I got a piercing over there.
I'm not gonna tell you where,
but I'll give you a hint.
It wasn't my nose or my ear
and it was one of my balls.
Well, regardless of what you think,
this is going to change
Mayor West's mind,
and we are gonna have
Jasper's wedding here.
Fine. Then until this is all over,
I'll stay somewhere else.
Come on, Stewie, we're going
to Grandma and Grandpa's.
Fine, I'll go,
but I'm not missing that gay wedding.
I still kick myself for missing
that topless cheerleader parade
with the 100-foot chocolate teddy bear
and the F-16s doing aerial acrobatics,
choreographed to the music of Queen.
Oh, I remember that day.
Huh. Should have gone to that thing.
My petition! What the hell are you doing?
I'm going to get to touch
right-wing boob because of this.
You idiot! Now I'm going to have
to get 10,000 more signatures
before tomorrow morning.
What were you thinking?
You don't understand, Brian.
When was the last time
you were even with a woman?
- Uh, when did the Challenger blow up?
- '86.
Yeah, it was like three years before that.
Mayor West, here's the gay marriage ban
for your approval.
Excellent. This is so important,
I'm going to sign it with all capital letters.
It's going to say, "ADAM WEST."
That's what it's going to say, you'll see.
Hey, buddy, you can't go in there.
Mayor West, you have to look at this.
Ten thousand signatures.
I've been up for 24 hours,
I paid off a few people
and I did a few things
in West Quahog I'm not proud of.
So, it's a show
about three hookers and their mom?
This is very impressive,
but my decision stands.
No!
Come on, buddy, you're leaving.
No, I can't let Jasper down.
I'm not going to let you sign that.
Go on, get out of here.
I should warn you,
I have a tiny bullet-proof shield,
the exact size of a bullet,
somewhere on my body.
And if you hit it, I'll be unharmed,
and your plan will be foiled.
You'll be the laughingstock of me.
I don't want to shoot you, Mayor West.
Good, because I'm incredibly crafty.
Hey, what's that on the ceiling?
Now I'm over here.
Look, this has gotten out of hand, I know.
I don't want anyone to get hurt.
But you can put an end to this right now
by tearing up that gay marriage ban.
You won't break me.
15 years ago
I swallowed everything I needed
to escape from a hostage situation.
A wall!
Well, no matter.
I'm prepared
for a lengthy captivity as well.
I swallowed this People magazine in 1989.
All right, Paul Hogan,
tell me about the real Crocodile Dundee.
It's so nice to have you home, dear.
I can take it or leave it.
God, this is such
an old-people house, you know.
I mean, look at this candy jar.
Let's, uh, take a look in here.
Let's see what you got here. You got...
You got licorice. Oh, that's, uh, that's...
Oh, Freedent. Oh, that's good.
Yeah, I got a sweet tooth,
I think I'll have some Freedent.
What's this? A cough drop.
A Luden's cough drop.
Is that candy? No, I don't think
that's candy. I think it's a cough drop!
What else we got? Look. Look at this.
There's a fishing lure in here.
There's a fishing lure in the candy jar.
What?
Am I supposed to eat this?
Eat a fishing lure?
Hey, look, Brian's on TV.
And now,
some Channel five exclusive footage
of the crazed homosexual gunman
who's taken Mayor West hostage.
Oh, my God!
Brian's taken the Mayor hostage?
Is this an eyeglass lens?
I didn't realize
how strongly he feels about this.
Gay marriage.
Next thing you know, they'll want to vote.
Oh, oh, look at this.
A spare key for a Volkswagen Scirocco.
They don't even make this anymore.
They don't even make this car anymore.
Whose key could this possibly be?
What if Brian's right?
I mean, certainly the love between a man
and a woman should be sacred, but...
Who's talking about love?
We're talking about marriage.
Well, don't you love Mom?
Come on, Lois, look at her.
So two straight people
who hate each other
have more of a right to be together
than two gay people who love each other?
That's what we raised you to believe.
Oh, my God! I've made a terrible mistake!
I've been brainwashed,
like Elizabeth Smart.
It's so wonderful having her home again.
She's brought music back into the house.
Playing songs on the harp.
Of course most of them
are about rape, but it's still nice.
I think I made Brian crazy.
Maybe I shouldn't have burned
that petition.
No, Chris, you did the right thing.
It's only a matter of time
before Mayor West signs that bill,
and you'll get to touch these.
Oh, boy, I got a feeling that
before the end of the day,
I'm going to be burying my dog.
Whoa, whoa. I said you could touch
my boobs. Let's start with that.
Look, Peter, if you can't get Brian
to come out peacefully,
we're going to have to take him down.
Don't worry, Joe,
I'm good with tight situations.
Like when I saved Luke Skywalker's life.
Okay, Luke, this will keep you warm
until I get the shelter built.
You're sure this is okay?
Yeah, you're just cutting into the fat.
All right, Brian, Peter's coming in.
I'll relax him by using my catchphrase.
Hey, what's up with you?
- What the hell was that?
- My catchphrase.
You don't have a catchphrase.
Why you gotta say like that?
Excuse me.
Would anyone like to play Stratego?
I have Stratego.
Oh, Peter, I never meant
for this to happen.
This whole situation
has totally spiraled out of control.
Brian, listen to me. I was wrong.
If two people love each other,
they should have the right to get married.
But you have to come down
and give yourself up.
If you drag this out any longer,
you're only hurting your own cause.
She's right. I'm sorry, Mayor West.
Well, you were only doing
what you thought was right, Brian.
And, hey, you've distracted everyone
from the Dig 'Em statue,
so I guess we don't need this bill anymore.
Everybody happy!
Well, it sure was nice of Mayor West
to drop the kidnapping charges.
It's amazing. All he asked for in return
was the key to a Volkswagen Scirocco.
You're welcome.
Listen, Lois,
I really appreciate
you putting your discomfort aside,
so we could have the wedding here.
Oh, please, I'm over all that now.
Two men getting married
doesn't bother me in the least.
They deserve happiness.
Everybody gay!
Thank you for watching «Family Guy» on
www.FOX-fan.ru